

CONTACT:



+48 884-960-930



konradbieniek@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/konrad-bieniek-73779b17a



https://github.com/Pan-be



Bielsko-Biała

SKILLS:

- Html
- CSS
- Java Script
- React
- .Git
- Wordpress
- npm
- PHP
- MySQL
- Node.js (basics)
- Canva
- Photoshop

SOFT SKILS:

- SCRUM
- Creativity
- · Aesthetic sense
- Critical thinking
- Design knowledge
- Skills for problem solving

LANGUAGES:

- Polish mother tongue
- English B2
- German A2
- Spanish A1

Konrad Bieniek

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

(REACT)

ABOUT ME:

I am a self-taught programmer and passionate about internet technologies. I began to take an interest in web developing in high school. I ran my first project: static website written in html and css. As a young adult, I gave up passion for work because I thought adulthood was not the time for passions. Today, as a mature person, I want to follow a path that I find interesting and do work not only to pay the bills, but also for growth and satisfaction. That's why two years ago I started studying front-end intensively, and today, as a junior js developer in the react framework, I'm ready to turn passion into work.

Privately, in addition to internet technology, I enjoy photography (especially taken with a drone), playing sports - such as calisthenics and playing soccer with my sons. I also like to occasionally take a break from a world full of technology by going camping in the woods.

PROJECTS:

• FE module to order food (React): live | github

Expense Tracker (React):

| live | github|

Simple Goals list (React)

live | github

live | github

Hangman game (JS)

Wallet with two color themes (JS) live | github
 CV webpage (HTML+CSS) live | github

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

LUCRUM GAMES SP. Z O.O.

Sales representative, website administrator (WordPress), March 2022 - currently

in addition to customer service and acquiring new ones, I administer and manage the website. I have improved the complaint system by creating a simple form, and at the moment I am working on an application for creating orders by customers. The technology I will be using in it is react, and at a later stage I plan to connect it to a database (probably firebase).

•

GOLDBERG&SONS

Telephone Customer Service->Customer Advisor->Team Leader, 2010-2016

Six years spent at Eu4Ya Goldberg & Sons helped me develop high skills as a salesperson and customer advisor. I got to know the financial market from the practical side. The work required me to be conscientious, determined and focused on the result. In this job I discovered my soft skills such as the ability to work in a group, and at a later stage to manage a small group of people

I'd be happy to tell more about my experience.

EDUCATION:

University of Economics in Katowice major: finance and accounting, 2009-2011

Technical School of Hotel Management and Tourism in Bielsko-Biała 2005-2009

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).